entangledpublishing.com 2018-10-28

# Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Entangled Publishing LLC. Your privacy is very important to us, and we want to make your shopping experience with us a safe and enjoyable environment. 

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, this privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**How we use the information we collect**

Some pages on our site may ask you to provide personal information, such as when you request to follow an author or register during our checkout process. If you have opted-in to receive email communications from Entangled during any such transactions, you may receive periodic emails about products and services until you opt-out using one of the clearly specified methods in every email communication.

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer, which enables us to customize our site to better suit your preferences. For example, a "cookie" could store your log-in information so that you do not need to register for every subsequent download that requires a form. In all cases, you can set your browser to choose not to accept cookies, but doing so may require you to re-enter certain information at each visit, or prevent us from customizing the site's features according to your preferences. 

**Third parties**

Entnagled will never sell or share personally identifiable information with an unaffiliated third party for any reason.

**Use of information**

We will only use your personally identifiable information as described below, unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personally identifiable information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you or notification to you:

  * We may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your direct inquires.
  * We will use your personally identifiable information to add you to our mailing lists and to send you emails from time to time. (Opt Out Available)
  * Maintain or administer the Site, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Site, and the products and services we offer.
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
  * We may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the Terms and Conditions for the Web Site.
  * We may transfer your personally identifiable information in connection with the sale, merger or change of control of Entangled, in which your personally identifiable information is associated.
  * Non-personal or aggregate information may be shared with any number of parties, provided that such information shall not specifically identify you.

**Consent**

By using this Site, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States.

**Changes to privacy policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Such changes will be effective immediately upon posting to this Site. Your continued use of this Site after any modification to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification. If we make any material revisions to this Privacy Policy, we will provide prominent notice by additional reasonable means.

**Opt-out process**

To opt-out of any future promotions from us, you can unsubscribe using the link at the bottom of any communication from Entangled We will process your request within a reasonable amount of time after receipt. 

**Contact us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a4d7d1d4d4cbd6d0e4c1cad0c5cac3c8c1c0d4d1c6c8cdd7cccdcac38ac7cbc9).

Other ways to contact us:

PHONE: 877-677-9451 Mon –Fri: 8am – 5pm PST

MAIL: Entangled Publishing LLC, 2614 S Timberline Rd Ste 105, Fort Collins CO 80525

Please provide the email address associated with your Program account when contacting Customer Service.

#### RECOMMENDED BOOKS FOR YOU
